gametap.com 2009-02-25

# GameTap - Privacy Policy

GAMETAP ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting GameTap. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this website and in the GameTap service.

THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

At some GameTap, LLC. sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At some other GameTap, LLC. sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card, to send a link or message to a friend about GameTap products or services, or the site, or other material, and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages or when you utilize the GameTap service, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS )the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), your activities while visiting our web pages, and your activities while using the GameTap service (e.g., which of our web pages you viewed, or which games within the GameTap service you played, etc.). Functions within the GameTap desktop application will automatically transmit this data back to us on a regular basis.

HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION

We may use the information you provide about yourself and any other information we collect about you to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings (including, without limitation, customer service inquiries), and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for customer service assistance, for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts, messages, or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with the GameTap service and our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate your participation and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.

We sometimes use information that we collect to improve the design and content of our service and to enable us to personalize your experience with us. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations or our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

Agents and contractors of GameTap, LLC. who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for GameTap, LLC..

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

Certain GameTap, LLC. sites may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that may want to market products or services to you. If we share personally identifiable information with third parties, we will provide you with notice prior to sharing such information.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.

Finally, GameTap will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

back to top

COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

To enhance your experience with our websites and the GameTap service, many of our web pages use "cookies" and "web beacons." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages ( e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

"Web beacons" or clear.gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on our sites from time to time for this and other purposes.

back to top

COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES, AD SERVERS AND SPONSORS

GameTap and other GameTap, LLC. websites may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

GameTap and other GameTap, LLC. websites sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. GameTap, LLC. has no control over these third parties' use of this information. The GameTap, LLC. site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

GameTap and other GameTap, LLC. websites may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. For more information on such third-party ad servers, please see the section below, entitled "Third-Party Ad Servers".

back to top

OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY

We put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures in an effort to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

back to top

HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT INFORMATION

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this GameTap, LLC. site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please follow the directions at the bottom of this policy.

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

back to top

SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS

Visitors to GameTap's website may participate in activities without providing any personally identifiable information. However, if a user wants to receive emails from GameTap, or wants to access GameTap's broadband gaming network, we ask the user to provide us with personal information, including name, screen name, e-mail address, gender, and/or age information. If a visitor to GameTap's website self-identifies as under 13 years of age, we will either collect no personally identifiable information from that individual, inform the child that a parent's verifiable consent is required, or we will collect the e-mail address of the user's parent in addition to the user's e-mail address. We use the parent's e-mail address to seek the parent's verifiable consent or notify the parent of his/her child's online activities and enable the parent to unsubscribe his/her child from a newsletter or other similar activity. For children joining the GameTap service, we will ask parents to create sub accounts and obtain their prior consent prior to collecting personally identifiable information from their children. If a user is under 13, we will not condition his/her participation in an online activity on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity. We do not share children's personally identifiable information with outside third parties not bound by this privacy notice for their own marketing purposes.

Please send a letter or postcard to our Privacy Manager at the mailing address provided below if you would like to review any of the personally identifiable information we have collected online from your child, or if you would like to do any of the following:

  * access personally identifiable information that GameTap's website has collected online from your child,
  * correct factual errors in such information,
  * request to have this information deleted, or
  * request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

Please be sure to include your e-mail address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child. If you have any questions, or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at the e-mail address, mailing address or telephone number listed below.

back to top

HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns about the GameTap, LLC. online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@gametap.com](mailto:customer.support@gametap.com).

back to top

UPDATES & EFFECTIVE DATE

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about August 26, 2005.

back to top

UNSUBSCRIBING & ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

If you have signed up to receive our emails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing email you receive from GameTap.

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this GameTap, LLC. site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please follow the instructions below.

back to top

THIRD-PARTY AD SERVERS

We and our advertisers may use third parties to serve or present the ads that appear on our site and to conduct research about the advertisements. Below is a representative list of such third parties and a link to their privacy notices. For more information, clink on the links below. For more information about third-party ad servers generally, visit [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)  
Atlas DMT: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or <http://www.atlasdmt.com/privacy/>  
Bluestreak: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or <http://www.bluestreak.com/privacy/privacy.asp>  
DoubleClick: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy>  
Eyeblaster: <http://www.eyeblaster.com/privacy.asp>  
Dynamic Logic: <http://www.dynamiclogic.com/privacy_policy.php>  
Klipmart: <http://www.klipmart.com/>  
Millward Brown IntelliQuest: <http://www.intelliquest.com/privacy/intro.asp>  
Unicast: <http://www.unicast.com/privacy-policy.shtml>

back to top

You may send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of the personally identifiable information that this site has collected about you online. For verification purposes, please include your first name, last name, and e-mail address.

Privacy Manager  
384 Northyards Boulevard, Building 500  
Atlanta, GA 30313 

e-mail: [privacy@gametap.com](mailto:customer.support@gametap.com)

back to top
